



Aqeel Ur Rehman Chishti

Nationality: Pakistani (+92) 3142881710 **Date of birth:** 20/05/1996

Email address: aqeel.chishti@outlook.com

Website: https://aqeelchishti.github.io/

○ Whatsapp Messenger: +923142881710

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ageelchishti/

• Address: House # 88, Block-F, Tariq Garden, 54000 Lahore (Pakistan)

ABOUT ME

I'm currently looking for a full-time Frontend Developer position. I'm an experienced SvelteKit Frontend Developer having 3+ years of experience in Svelte / SvelteKit, Tailwind CSS, Typescript & Javascript ES6, Django, and WordPress & Elementor. Moreover, I have specialized 1+ years of experience in Vulnerability Assessment & Management, Penetration Testing, Reconnaissance, Open-source Intelligence, System & Application Auditing, and Red Teaming Operations.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Security Analyst | Internship

Bytesuit LLC [07/2021 - 02/2022]

City: Bahawalpur Country: Pakistan

Penetration Tester & Cyber Operations Training | Apprenticeship

National Cyber Training Program (NCTP) [07/2020 - 09/2021]

City: Bahawalpur **Country:** Pakistan

Conduct penetration testing on several Live VM Cloud Network Environments, Websites & Web Applications, and then Report on Findings. Including Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing.

SvelteKit Frontend Developer | Freelancing

Several worldwide different employer's on Upwork & Fiverr [08/2019 - Current]

City: Bahawalpur **Country:** Pakistan

Working experience in SvelteKit Development, Python/Django Development, Landing page, Website & Web Application Development, and Web Designing.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (Hons.)

National College of Business Administration & Economics (NCBA&E) [15/03/2015 - 30/08/2019]

Address: 31-A Model Town A, Sarwar Shaheed Road, 63100 Bahawalpur (Pakistan)

https://ncbae.edu.pk/

Field(s) of study: Computer Science



Final grade: CGPA: 3.5/4.0

Thesis: Marble Crafts Ecommerce Store

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Full Stack Development (Django & SvelteKit)

Javascipt / Typesript / Python / HTML & CSS / SvelteKit / Django / Object Oriented Programming (OOP) / Django REST Framework / Python Web Automation / Web Scraping / Bootstrap 5 / Svelte Js / Tailwind CSS / Wordpress + Elementor / Javascript (ES6) / Git

Information Security

Penetration Testing / Vulnerability Assessment / Linux (terminal commands, Bash/Shell) / Information Security / C ybersecurity / WPScan / SQLMap / Open Source Intelligence (OSINT) / Penetration Test (Kali tools, Nessus, CVE) / Wireshark / Metasploit Framework / OWASP Top 10 / Burp Suite / Web Application Security Testing / Nessus / Kali Linux / Nmap

HONOURS AND AWARDS

Ethical Hacker Nanodegree

Udacity [28/06/2021] https://confirm.udacity.com/TLEEUM7L

Penetration Testing, Network Defense & Cyber Operations

National Cyber Training Program (NCTP) [09/2021] https://aqeelchishti.github.io/docs/pentest-pdf.png https://aqeelchishti.github.io/docs/network_defence-pdf.png

Technical Support Fundamentals

Coursera [12/09/2020]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/9P9ZNB3RYQQ9

The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking

Coursera [29/09/2020]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/V4XW2JFTUNAP

Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User

Coursera [16/10/2020]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/6QP35BAMRN3P

Crash Course on Python

Coursera [24/12/2020]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/FPRTQQF3KVSM

Linux Command Line professional

Codecademy Pro [04/09/2020]

https://ageelchishti.github.io/docs/Codecademy bash scripting certificate-ageel-chishti.pdf



Python for Security Professional

Cybrary [09/01/2020]

https://ageelchishti.github.io/docs/cybrary-cert-python-for-security-professionals.pdf

Certificate of Proficiency in Information Systems Management (CPISM)

Aptech Computer Education [09/02/2015]

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Urdu

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Working on Pentesting Training Platforms

I really like to work with Penetration Testing training platforms and learn with real-world scenarios. I have already joined platforms like Hack The Box and Try Hack Me.

Designing Websites and Web Automation

During my studies, I have done several Web Design and Automation projects.

Gaming

I also like playing First Person Shooter games.

Playing Badminton

I'm also a badminton player and I took part in several tournaments on the community level in my local area.